SRIRAM PK UI/UX Designer

ABOUT ME

I'm a UI/UX/IX Designer and Prototyper. I'm passionate about User centered design and love crafting products that solve real problems.

I research, communicate, prototype, design, test, document, organize and deliver.

I have 4+ years of enterprise experience that includes designing at Apple and internship at a design agency(Monigle)

Hit me up to know more about my work and process.

PORTFOLIO

www.srirampk.com

EMAIL

uxsriram@gmail.com

SKILLS

DESIGN

Storyboarding, Journey mapping, User personas, Wireframing, Interactive prototypes, Mockups, Information Architecture, Visual design

RESEARCH

A/B testing, Contextual inquiry, Wizard of Oz, Affinity diagrams, Flow and sequence models, Think alouds, Heuristic evaluation, Web analytics, Surveys and Usability analysis.

TOOLS

DESIGN PROTOTYPING

Sketch Invision
Photoshop Framer
Illustrator Principle
Balsamiq Marvel
Justinmind Axure
Zeplin

EXPERIENCE

UI/UX Designer, Apple, Inc., SF Bay Area, CA

September 2018 - Present

- Contributing to the UX & UI of apple's internal product development teams.
- Responsible for research, stakeholder interviews, wireframes, mockups, design deliverables.
- Curated an internal design sketch library and documented guidelines for those seeking design and UX help.

UI/UX Design Intern, Monigle, Denver, CO

May 2018 - August 2018

- Contributed to the UX & UI of new BEAM product features
- Guided the management, layout and loading of content to client brand management systems
- Worked closely in support of internal development, product and client experience teams

Product Designer, Pobyt

June 2017 - May 2018

- Solely responsible for product design and user experience of Pobyt, a hotel reservation app for short stays.
- Followed agile approach: user interviews, design, feedback and rapid iterations
- Managed a team of 8 (designers and developers)

Business Analyst, S&P Global Market Intelligence

Jun 2015 - Dec 2016

- Worked on designing user interfaces for their data collection web applications.
- Notable projects include Celsus, GICS and Hub.
- Worked closely with the QA team to evaluate the usability of the product.

Design Intern, Etyacol Technologies

Jan 2015 - June 2015

- Responsible for User Interface Design of Cashkumar web application and dashboard.
- Created several graphic design posters for social media engagement.

EDUCATION

University of North Carolina, Charlotte, USA *M.S.,Human Computer Interaction*

Vellore Institute of Technology, India *M.S.,Software Engineering*